[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120815pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 39, "question": "How are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 40, "answer": "Good to hear it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120815pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 49, "question": "He's a bit of a problem for you, isn't he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 50, "answer": "You know, actually I don't think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120815pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 68, "question": "If the American public just basically don't want to pay more tax, aren't they going to lean in an election in economic hard times towards the party that is saying, I'm not going to hit you in the pocket so hard?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "RB", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 69, "answer": "Well, again, we've got to get out of political cliches.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120815pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", "CC", "VBZ", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "NNP", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "RBR", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 95, "question": "What did you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 96, "answer": "Piers, this is really what I recoil about in where our politics is getting now and is being fueled by super PAC money, is being fueled by a media that becomes so much more obsessed with sound bites than substance.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120815pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 106, "question": "I mean does your anger extend to that kind of stuff?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 107, "answer": "Well, I think that I've been clear on the record about my feelings about these super PACs and the negativity on both sides.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120815pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "NNP", ",", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 119, "question": "When you take all these things into consideration, you must be disappointed that the president isn't ordering some new form of gun control, aren't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 120, "answer": "So, Piers, two points.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120815pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 181, "question": "Hi, Piers, how are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 182, "answer": "You're very nice to me.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120815pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "WP", "IN", ":", "WP", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 213, "question": "Had he said shackles rather than chains, had he said that, would it have made any difference to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "NNS", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 214, "answer": "IULIANI: Well, what about -- what about -- I have no idea.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120815pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 235, "question": "How would you describe your honest reaction?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 236, "answer": "No, no, I wasn't -- I wasn't shocked or dismayed.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Governor Romney"]}, "docId": "120815pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 254, "question": "-- and the public don't buy into him at the election, that's a problem, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 255, "answer": "I think that Governor Romney has made a gamble here.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120815pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 291, "question": "To Grover, you're obviously now into pre-election mode which I would imagine means you're going to be even more aggressive about this than normal, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "RBR", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "IN", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 292, "answer": "Sure, if you want.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Grover"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120815pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 305, "question": "So Michael Linden, from your point of view, where is the best attack line for the Democrats?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", "."], "aSentId": 306, "answer": "Well, the best attack line for the Democrats is just looking at the details of the plan.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael Linden"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120815pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 319, "question": "What do you do about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 320, "answer": "Well, there are two things.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}, "docId": "120815pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 370, "question": "What do you want to say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 371, "answer": "What Obama did is he's just changed the rules.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120815pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 396, "question": "What do you make of the way they are all going at each other now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 397, "answer": "ATHER: Well, I think it's gotten worse.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120815pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 410, "question": "It would be very interesting to see how well the Republicans do at their convention in changing the conversation back to do you agree with Obama or not Obama, rather than do you agree with Paul Ryan and his plan or not?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "WRB", "RB", "DT", "NNPS", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "NNP", ",", "RB", "IN", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 411, "answer": "He's definitely resonating with the American public.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama", "Obama", "Paul Ryan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120815pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 441, "question": "And it would be truly ironic if it was that that cost Mitt Romney the election, wouldn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "DT", "NN", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 442, "answer": "It would be ironic.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120815pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "RB", "VBP", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 478, "question": "Are you surprised by it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 479, "answer": "I'm not surprised because people always have something to say.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120815pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 505, "question": "So what was harder, \"Dancing With the Stars\", that or getting in a ring pounding somebody away as the try to beat you up?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "VBD", "JJR", ",", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "DT", "NNP", "''", ",", "IN", "CC", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 506, "answer": "Well, you make this sound so --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120815pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 507, "question": "Real?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 508, "answer": "Anyway, they're all different.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120815pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJS", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 514, "question": "What is the best and worst thing about being Mohammed Ali's daughter?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "CC", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 515, "answer": "The best thing, just off the top of my head, is just knowing that I have that same blood running through my veins.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Mohammed Ali"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120815pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 538, "question": "Actually, it's been great to meet you because you're a chip off the old block really, aren't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "RP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 539, "answer": "A little bit.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]